http://www.duncraft.com/privacy_policy

Close Menu
Log In
Create Account
FeedersAll Bird FeedersSquirrel Proof FeedersCaged Bird FeedersNyjer Seed Bird FeedersSquirrel Resistant FeedersDuncraft Brand FeedersHopper Bird FeedersTube Bird FeedersWindow Bird FeedersSuet and Block FeedersHummingbird FeedersOriole Bird FeedersPlatform FeedersFruit & Nut FeedersBluebird FeedersDecorative Bird FeedersPole-Mount Bird Feeders
FoodsAll Bird SeedNo-Waste! No-Mess SeedsBird Seed Blends & MixesSuet Cakes, Balls & PlugsBird Seed Blocks, Cakes & BarsMealworms & Insect FoodsWildlife, Corn & NuggetsFruits, Nuts & JellyBird Seed TreatsHummingbird & Oriole NectarHot Pepper FoodsSeed Storage & Scoops
BathsAll Bird BathsPedestal Bird BathsSolar Powered Bird BathsWater Misters & DrippersHanging Bird BathsDecorative Bird BathsGround Bird BathsDeck Mounted Bird BathsHeated Baths & HeatersFountains & Water WigglersBird Bath Accessories
HousesAll Bird HousesBluebird HousesBestBasic HousesSongbird & Roosting BoxesDecorative HousesHummingbird HousesPurple Martin HousesBird House AccessoriesNesting MaterialsBat Houses
AccessoriesBrackets, Hangers & PostsSquirrel Baffles & GuardsCleaning SuppliesWindow Strike SolutionsSeed Trays for Tube FeedersParts for Duncraft ProductsHummingbird AccessoriesSeed Storage & Scoops
CrittersSquirrel Feeders & HousesSquirrel FoodsSquirrel Baffles & GuardsSquirrel DeterrentsPoultry SuppliesButterflies & Insects
GiftsGarden DecorNature GiftsOutdoor Pest ControlsWind and WeatherGuides - Books - DVD's
New
Exclusives
Sale
eGift Certificates
Gift Cards
Customer Service
Contact Us
Home
Shop early to get your gifts in time for the holidays. »
0 items
MENU
Share the joy of birds with friends and family! Shop early to get your gifts in time for the holidays. »
Free Shipping
on orders $75+   CODE: DC75
shop by category
get help
We Know Birds
Questions about birds? Or maybe something about your order? Ask our friendly experts.
Call
(888) 879-5095
Weekdays 8:30am-5:00pm Eastern
Email
Chat
your account
Sign In/Create Account
Orders
Free Shipping
Enjoy free economy shipping on orders of $75+ to any address in the 48 contiguous states. Simply add the code to the Add Promo Code field in your shopping cart, located under the proceed to checkout button! Offers cannot be combined, one code per order.
View Cart0 Items
your account
Sign In/Create Account
Orders
Account
Wishlist
Help Center
(888) 879-5095
Your Privacy
At Duncraft, we are committed to respecting your privacy and protecting the security of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains the type of information we gather, how we use it, and how we protect it. By visiting Duncraft.com, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy.
We reserve the right to modify our privacy practices and update this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any substantial changes to the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
Please contact our customer service team with any questions.
Why do we collect your information?
First and foremost, we collect information so we can fulfill your requests for specific products and services. Once you place an order with us or set up an account, you’re no longer an anonymous stranger; you’re part of the Duncraft community! This information helps us customize the content that you see, fine-tune your shopping and browsing experience, and let you know about specials and new products.
Information we gather
We may collect information from you when we correspond via telephone, chat, email, product reviews, and blog comments.
When you place an order or set up an account at Duncraft, we collect information such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, billing information (credit card number, expiration date, and billing address), any promotion codes used, and products purchased.
(If you are shipping a gift directly to the recipient, we also collect the name and address of that recipient.) We do not store your credit card information in our database, and we do not share or sell email addresses, telephone numbers, or any information from your wish lists.
When you request to receive our blog via email or subscribe to our online newsletter, we collect your name and email address. We may also ask for your zip code, gender, and areas of interest. If you enter our contests or other promotions, you may be asked for information necessary to fulfill the promotion.
Some information is automatically collected when you visit our website and blogs. For example, we may collect your IP address, access times, referring website addresses, browser type and language, and usage and activity on our site. We do not collect your name or email address unless you provide it. If you access our site from a mobile device, we may also collect information about the type of mobile device you used, your device’s unique ID, the type of mobile internet browsers you use, and information about the location of the device.
Our website is not intended for use by children under the age of 14, and we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 14. If we become aware that we have collected such information without the consent of the child’s parent or guardian, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete the information.
How do we use this information?
We maintain the data that you provide us, along with a record of your transactions, in a secure database.
We use the information you provide in checkout so we can ship your order and contact you if we have a question about your order. After you place an order with us, you will receive an email confirmation that we have received your order. You will receive this email only if you have provided your correct email address during checkout. Recipients of eGift certificates will receive an email notifying them of the gift and instructing them how to redeem it.
From time to time, we may share your name and address with other companies whose products we think you may be interested in. We never share or sell email addresses or telephone numbers. Please contact us to opt out of that service.
Within a month of your purchase, you will receive a Duncraft free e-newsletter with great bird feeding tips at your email address; this mailing has an unsubscribe link at the bottom of each mailing. You can follow that link to reduce the frequency of our emails or to unsubscribe completely.
Information we share with others
We contract with other companies to provide certain services, such as shipping and payment processing. We provide these companies with only the information they need to provide their services, and they are prohibited from using this information for any other purpose.
Links to other sites
We provide links to other sites we think you will find informative and useful. These sites have their own privacy and security policies. We recommend that you review these policies at any site you visit.
Cookies and Pixel Tags
A cookie is a small data file that your web browser stores on your computer.
We use a cookie to help make it easier for you to use our site. Cookies enable you to place an order on our website, and they allow us to enhance and personalize your online shopping experience so the content you receive is more relevant to you. Your browser must be set to accept cookies before you can place an order on our website. The Help feature on most browsers will tell you how to block, customize, or allow cookies. If you have set your browser to not accept cookies, please call us at 888-879-5095 Monday-Friday from 8:30am to 5:00pm ET to place your order.
Pixel tags are tiny graphic images that we use to learn what parts of our website you have visited.
They also help us improve our website by learning how effective any of your searches were.
Pixel tags also enable us to send you email in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an email message from us.
We sometimes contract with third party advertising companies to place Duncraft ads across the internet. They may use cookies and pixel tags to garner information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements. These targeted advertisements may then appear on other sites that you visit. This information is completely anonymous, and absolutely no personally identifiable information is collected in this process.
Security
We have instituted reasonable safeguards to help ensure that the information we collect is secure. Your Duncraft Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas Duncraft uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.
Opt Out/Corrections
Duncraft gives you the ability to edit your preferences at any time, including whether you want Duncraft to contact you about specials and new products. You may request deletion of your Duncraft account, reduce or eliminate marketing emails, or reduce or eliminate paper catalogs at any time. Just contact our customer service team and we’ll be happy to take care of your request.
Back to Top
Bird Feeders, Bird Houses, Bird Baths | Specialists in Wild Bird Feeding | Wild Bird Superstore Since 1952
Call Duncraft at 1.888.879.5095102 Fisherville Road, Concord, NH 03303.FAX 1.603.224.3925
©1996-2020 Duncraft, Inc. All Rights Reserved. Prices, specifications, and images are subject to change without notice.
